xtremegiveaway.com 2016-03-15

# 

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**  
**Your privacy is important to us, and to protect your privacy we are providing this notice explaining our online information collection practices and what choices you have about how your information is collected and used. This Privacy Notice is posted on every page on our website in the navigation on the bottom of each page.**  
**  
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT:** This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our SportEAR website. On some pages, you may be requested to register prior to using our services. After registering you can place orders for products, register for online contests, upload comments and photos, and receive information and limited online specials that we may offer from time to time. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information ONLY if you are purchasing products online 

**  
HOW WE USE INFORMATION:** We use the information you provide about yourself prior to your ordering products or to be able to use the various services on our site reserved for registered users. We do not share or sell this information to any outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and to provide reasonable notification of any new service and updates. Email addresses collected are not shared with outside parties.

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to improve our website or to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of men or women have visited certain areas on our website, or have become registered users, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**  
OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY:** To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
**  
OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:** Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.   
**  
HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION:** You can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into our site and reviewing your contact information. Note: you must log in to access your account information.

We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows any errors.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**  
REMARKETING POLICY:** This website uses the Google AdWords and other remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the SportEAR website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.  
**  
HOW TO CONTACT US:** Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-866-422-5502 or send an email to [support@sportear.com](mailto:support@sportear.com).  
**  
OPTING OUT:** If you would like to unsubscribe, please call us at 1-866-422-5502 or send an email to [support@sportear.com](mailto:support@sportear.com).
